https://uspystore.com/privacy-policy/

Zone Shield EZ DVR
Hidden Cameras (Hardwired)
Zone Shield EZ DVR
Hidden Cameras (Hardwired)
Privacy Policy
U-SPY ENTERPRISES, INC. DBA U-SPY STORE AND ITS AFFILIATES (THE "COMPANY") ARE COMMITTED TO PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY AND DO NOT SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH ADVERTISERS OR ANY OTHER THIRD PARTY, NOR DO WE OTHERWISE ALLOW SUCH THIRD PARTIES ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION. Please read the following policy to understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you may provide to us via this site (the "U-Spy Site"). This statement may be revised from time to time, so please revisit this page often to remain fully informed of our commitment.
What Information Does the Company Collect from You?
The Company collects two types of information from you: (i) personally identifiable information, and (ii) technical and other information.
Personally Identifiable Information. When you make a purchase through the U-Spy Site, we request that you provide us personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, billing information, and email address.
Technical and Other Information. While you are browsing our site, we automatically log your IP address (a number assigned to your computer when you use the Internet) and your activity while using our site. Additionally, in order to personalize and enhance your experience on our website, we may also collect information through "cookies." Cookies are small strings of text that are sent by our site to your browser and then stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. We also use cookies to gather broad demographic information and to help identify you in respect to visits to our site so that we may improve your user experience, and to determine whether you visited our site from a particular Internet link or advertisement. While a code in the cookie file enables our site to label you as a particular user, including identifying you by name, address, or other personally identifiable information, such cookie files are encrypted in order to protect your information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but it is possible to change your browser setup so that it does not accept cookies.
How Is Your Information Used?
We collect, retain, and use the information we collect via the U-Spy Site for legitimate business purposes only, including, without limitation, the following: to correspond with you regarding your purchase(s) via our site, to inform you of developments about the Company or the Company’s products/services that we believe may be of interest to you, to monitor site visitor traffic patterns and site usage, to comply with applicable laws, to enforce our Terms of Use and to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our users, and others.
Modifications
We strive to maintain the accuracy of your information, and we will use our commercially reasonable efforts to respond promptly to update our database if you advise us that the information in our database is not accurate. In addition, at any time after signing up to receive email communications from us, you may elect to stop receiving such communications, or you may update or modify the information that you previously provided to us, by contacting us at info@uspystore.com.
Children
In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, 15 U.S.C. §§ 6501-06 and 16 C.F.R. §§ 312.1-312.12, our site does not permit children under 13 years of age to become users, and we do not collect information from children. By using our site, you represent that you are not under 13 years of age.
Protecting Your Personally-Identifiable Information
The Company employs security systems to protect the information we receive from you from unauthorized disclosure. If you suspect unauthorized access to your information, it is your responsibility to contact the Company immediately. Please be aware that Internet data transmission is not always secure, and we cannot warrant that information you transmit utilizing this site is secure. Because security is important to both the Company and you, we will always make reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems.
Acceptance of These Terms
This Privacy Statement is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the U-Spy Site’s Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, please do not use this site.
Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
This Privacy Statement is effective as of June 1, 2006. (We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this statement, and any such modifications, alterations, or updates will be effective upon posting. In the event that we modify this Privacy Statement, your continued use of this site in light of changes to this Privacy Statement will signify your acceptance of the changes.
Questions?
Questions regarding this Privacy Statement should be directed to info@uspystore.com. The Company may also be contacted directly at the following address and phone number:
U-Spy Enterprises, Inc.2406 W Fullerton AveChicago, IL 60647Phone: (773) 529-2779
Connect with Us:
©
U-Spy Store
Sitemap
